<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <string name="notinitialized">
        Please read!\nThis is the human activity recognition module.
		The neural network for classification of activities is 
		currently not initialized.\nIn the settings the sensors and activities can be selected, 
		which should be supported by the activity recognition. Only enabeled Sensors are shown.
		Once selected, a new neural network can be created, 
		which is saved automaticlly.\nIf everything is done correctly the neural network can be 
		trained on this page.\nAttention: After creating and saving a neural network, changing 
		the sensors	will cause a deletion of the beforehand saved neural 
		network!
	</string>
	    <string name="initialized">		Please read!\nThe neural network is ready to get trained. In the training 
        menu it is possible to choose between live and previous 
        recorded data.\nIt is also possible to choose a time window - which 
        contains all the data - length, its standard value is 2000 
        milliseonds.\nIn the live training the neural network will be trained with 
        data which is currently recorded. The training starts 5 seconds 
        after pressting "Start training".\nTo train previous recorded data a period of time is needed, in 
        which the activity to train was performed. It is importat that
        all data in this periode of time completely, i.e. all sensors 
        that are supported now were collecting data in this specific 
        time periode too.\nThe training completely runs in the background and can be stopped 
        anytime on this screen. Also it will auto save the neural network 
        every 256 training epochs.\nPlease be aware of the fact, that once a training is done and 
        saved, it cannot be undone!\nAttention: After creating and saving a neural network, changing 
		the sensors	will cause a deletion of the beforehand saved neural 
		network!</string>
    
</resources>